http://www.lifelinescreening.com/privacy-policy

Privacy & Cookie PolicyWe understand that your health is an extremely private matter. That's why we have a strict privacy policy that we follow closely. You can rest assured that your privacy is something we respect and preserve in all aspects of our business.
Information collected on our site
Most of the information provided to you by Life Line Screening's web site (and the web sites of our affiliated entities, including Life Line Community Healthcare) is offered without our collecting any personally identifiable information from you. The only time you will be asked to provide personal information is if you wish to contact us using our online inquiry system, or sign up for our e-newsletter. You have a choice as to whether or not you would like to submit personal information such as your name, address, city, state, ZIP code and phone number to our online inquiry system. If you elect not to submit this information online, you may call (1.800.897.9177) or e-mail (info@llsa.com) our customer service department directly, and they will be happy to assist you.
Life Line will automatically collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the links you click and other actions taken on Life Line Screening's web site. We collect anonymous information about your use of our site through cookies. Cookies do not tell us who you are. The cookies collect standard information that your browser sends to every web site you visit, such as IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring web site addresses. Additionally, we may collect information such as which pages you visit, your length of stay on each page, and your navigation path.
If you make an appointment with us, additional personal information about you (name, address, e-mail, phone number) will be collected and stored in servers at our location.
How information is used
Life Line collects and uses your personal information to provide you with services you have requested. These services may include phone calls, e-mails or direct mail pieces sent to your home regarding screenings in your area.
Information collected from your visit to our web site is used to enhance and evaluate our web site.
How we may use your information:
The purposes for which you specifically provided the information, for example, to enable us to contact you regarding a submitted question or inquiry, confirm and remind you of a scheduled appointment, or notify you of upcoming screenings in your area
To send you e-mail notifications about upcoming screenings, to send you our e-newsletter, or to otherwise contact you
With your permission, we may share your name and address with marketing partners so they may contact you regarding relevant services.
We may be required by law to release your personal information if compelled by legal subpoenas, or when the law otherwise requires us to do so.
We enlist the services of third-party data management vendors to support high quality, lower cost, and faster production of your results letter. It is Life Line's policy to establish Business Associate Agreements with these vendors, to ensure that your information is used only for the purpose of results production, and that it is afforded the same degree of protection as Life Line provides. Life Line Screening maintains a copy of films and completed medical history questionnaires for four years from the date of the screening, after which point, obsolete records are destroyed to maintain participant's privacy.
Third-party access
When you submit your personal information on Life Line's web site, it will not be shared with third parties for marketing purposes without your written permission.
Opting out or changing your personal information
Life Line offers its customers choices for the collection, use and sharing of personal information. We offer you the opportunity to choose whether to receive certain communications from third parties at the time of your actual screening. To opt out of Life Line Screening's mailing list, please write to:
Life Line Screening
Attn: Marketing Department
6150 Oak Tree Blvd.
Independence, OH 44131
You can opt out of the e-newsletter online.
If you have received services from Life Line, you may make changes to your personal information by submitting your request or contacting our customer service department at 1.800.897.9177.
Security
All personal information is stored in limited-access servers. We use a number of security technologies and procedures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access or disclosure. Life Line will continue to maintain these safety measures to ensure the security of these servers and your personally identifiable information.
Changes to the privacy policy
Life Line reserves the right to modify the terms of this privacy policy. We will highlight any changes that are made to the policy, and we recommend that you revisit the policy from time to time.
